CV – Chris J Davies

Tlf.: 31 75 44 01

E-mail: thechrisjd@gmail.com
Website: http://thechrisjd.xyz
Address: Tomsgårdsvej 63 – 4.th,

2400 København NV



Personal profile

Original I come from the UK, but I have been living in Denmark for the last 2 years. This of course means that I am a native English speaker; however, I am currently studying Danish. Having a great passion for IT, especially programming, was the reason I chose to study web development at KEA. Since starting I have been faced with many challenges on both the front end and back end, helping to teach me how to be a full stack developer. In my spare time, I am working towards getting my CompTIA security+certification and learning other databases such as MongoDB. I enjoy going to the gym, biking, traveling, cooking and reading. I am diligent, self-motivated, problem solver and I always come to work with positive energy.

Education

2019- → BA in web development

- Full stack web development
- Ajax, one-page websites
- Sessions
- Input sanitization and encryption
- Databases
- Scrum

2019 → CompTIA Network+ certification

2017-2019 → AP degree in IT Technology

- Networking
- Programing in C# and python
- Windows server in virtual environments
- Management

$2012-2015 \rightarrow$ Studying in the UK

IT-Skills

- IT troubleshooting
- Experience with Cisco equipment
- Setting up and maintaining of virtual environments in VMware and virtual box
- Microsoft and Linux servers
- OS (windows, tails, kali, mint and mac)
- CSS, HTML, JavaScript, C#, python and PHP
- Ajax
- MySQL and PostgreSQL

Work Experience

2018-2019 → Freelance web development

2014-2018 → Working in the customer service industry

2014-2015 → Young enterprise, started and ran a business

Personal qualifications

- → Accommodating \rightarrow Loyal → Flexible \rightarrow Responsible - → Positive → Analytical

Websites

https://venner.xyz

- Social media website
- Ajax and sweet alert
- Sessions
- User input sanitization and encryption
- Databases MySQL
- Account activation via email
- Login and logout system
- Creating TLS keys and certificates
- Real time chat
- Posting system
- Friend request/acceptance system

Driving license

B – Personal car